Back for seconds.
Meg 2: The Trench is a action, science fiction,
horror film directed by Ben Wheatley.
An exploratory dive into the deepest depths of the ocean of a daring research team spirals into chaos when a
malevolent mining operation threatens their mission and forces them into a high-stakes battle for survival.
Jonas Taylor, played by Jason Statham.
Jiuming Zhang, played by Wu Jing.
Meiying, played by Shuya Sophia Cai.
DJ, played by Page Kennedy.
Montes, played by Sergio Peris-Mencheta.
Driscoll, played by Sienna Guillory.
Meg 2: The Trench (Chinese: 巨齿鲨2：深渊; titled Shark 2 in some territories) is a 2023 science fiction action film
directed by Ben Wheatley and a sequel to The Meg (2018), based on the 1999 novel The Trench by Steve Alten.
Jon Hoeber, Erich Hoeber, and Dean Georgaris all return as writers from the first film, with Jason Statham, Sophia Cai, Page
Kennedy, and Cliff Curtis reprising their roles alongside Wu Jing, Sergio Peris-Mencheta, and Skyler Samuels.
Like the previous film, it follows a group of scientists who must outrun and outswim the megalodons when a
malevolent mining operation threatens their mission and forces them into a high-stakes battle for survival.
Plans for the sequel were announced to be in early development in
October 2018 after the box office success of the first film.
Principal photography began in February 2022 and lasted until May,
occurring in various locations in Asia and Warner Bros.
Studios, Leavesden, in Watford, Hertfordshire, England.
Meg 2: The Trench had its premiere at the Shanghai International Film Festival on June 9,
2023, and was released in the United States on August 4, by Warner Bros.
The film received negative reviews but was a box office
success, grossing $397.8 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
deep sea, sequel, underwater, shark.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.